If I purposely cool the
top really fast or maybe
I make spots that I cool
fast, then what happens?
Well, this wants to
have volume a inside.
This wants to have volume--
well, this cools first.
So this cools first.
So inside, so what happens?
As I cool it now, I have this.
This is now a glass.
This is now a solid.
And I should say glass
solid, so it's solidified.
And this wants to
have a lower volume--
lower volume.
It wants a lower
volume, but that's
been frozen at a higher volume.
Why?
I cooled it faster.
That's it.
I cooled it faster, and now the
inside is like, wait a second,
I'm not cooling so fast.
I don't need such a high volume.
Can I please get a smaller
volume out of this?
And the top is like,
well, I'm already stuck.
I'm already a solid.
And what happens is it pulls.
And so what you get is
wants lower volume pulls
on the surface, and that
means that this is going
to be the top, if I'll
just draw it one more time,
will be under compression--
under compression,
and the inside
will be under tensile stress--
under tensile stress.